sufficiency while your hands still shake you drown
For about myself. Can you believe that you didn't like I googled that one important bombing
I googled that woman Martina big and it's like all his porno came up and then I had it still open
And then I like I was like where's my tabs on my whole screen shared and there's all this porn
And now people think I'm a pervert. I didn't see shit like we didn't see me
Nobody saw anything. Okay. Nothing was I think we see I
Mean honestly, I was looking at the fucking
my face looking and I clicked back and I was like oh shit and we were in the
studio I was like oh oh shit I'm talking to what's his face
I forget his name already
fuck yeah you're talking to me hey don't
no not you not you
another ghost ghost yeah see he's a ghost I forget
You guys didn't see anything and I wasn't oh, it's the screen. Okay. Well, no, I don't think so. I was gonna share something
I forgot what I was gonna share though. It's gonna show you something, but
Yeah, careful. That's why I had the coves on my tabs before I show
Yeah, exactly. I need much more careful. Um, it's uh, I think I have to go out of this browser to share even more easily
It's like I'm gonna change my camera
Or just enter a different browser
Right there
Holy shit
Try again
Oh now
Oh
Okay, I do know you're the real JD but oh yeah, I was looking at something
On I need to I just wanted to ask you about it. Let me see what can bring it back up
Okay
Yeah, okay, I'm
So is this what is what's going on here?
Yeah
Bring it up. Let's see
It's
Had your name
See okay, maybe I'm on the wrong
Didn't see something
Oh, yeah, okay, here we go. I'll share it screen
Yeah, I did it. What do you think about Andy dick?
Do you ever see when he got like beat up in my thoughts Vegas? That was pretty funny. Oh when he got punched
Yeah, he was like is a whole like bait at least it was better bet she's laughing. Okay, so this one
Yeah
Okay, JD just said I've never been this board watching. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I've never been this board watching. Thanks a lot. Okay, I
Know JD I know I know you think I don't know that you think I don't know that I know I obviously know
That's not that's not a piece to rock. I know you don't have to tell me that
not nice not nice okay I'm gonna try everything we're gonna go to that stupid
event right now I feel horrible like yeah yeah I might have
Look, okay, I'm a very expressive person.
If you're boring, I'm gonna let you know I'm bored.
If you're entertaining me, I'm gonna let you know I'm entertained.
I didn't mean to break her little heart
and for her to hold a grudge against me.
Oh my God, at least like.
That was what she got mad about?
I mean, I don't think so.
Like, cause I could tell like, she was like, I know, I know.
Like you could tell that she was like
not gonna stop at me right there, but.
She might have held on to that, but she might have held on to that, like it might have planted a little seed in her brain that I, because I always complain about her driving.
I'm bored. I'm bored. You're driving too much. Get out of the car. Walk around.
Like that, you know. Kind of like the troll her.
Ah, but I think she took it seriously. I think it was too much. I think I just out trolled her
Then I would call her high all the time and not even make sense sometimes, but you know
That's what people do. I was like, hey compared to all your other retards on the gym
Well, I mean, you're like, we're a lot more chaotic than I, like, I picture you'd be like, when I, you know, watching, watching you, you seem kind of like unassuming and like, you know, safe.
And it's like, you're, you're kind of dangerous, it sounds like.
I'm not, how am I, I'm an honest Christian woman, and I am not a Christian woman.
Okay.
No, no, I mean, I like it though. I mean, I like it. It's kind of like wow
I said I never saw the side beautiful, but I kind of like it
It's always like that. It's always like that. I'm assuming like nice good. Oh, look at this guy like Bobo
I'm gonna say you're like
you're exposing me sorry I'm sorry I'm just fucking I guess you could call me a troll not
an evil troll just a little bit of a troll I guess I pushed her too hard it was too much of me
saying that she was boring yeah handle me criticizing her being boring plus the body
Care about her. Mm-hmm. She's a nice lady sometimes, but I think it's just it's better off of that. I
Don't engage with a Lisa so much because if I have that much power to make her
Snap like that. I don't think like it's not healthy. Maybe even like around her
She's gonna be that mad about little things like a man like what if I was actually mad about something and I like
It was like at least I'm pissed off about something and she like looked at like I can't if she I don't know man
Like if she's gonna be that mad about something so small
Yeah, I mean it's like but she is very sensitive because she's a cancer right and so it's like
She just knows that I obviously want the best for her.
That's why I'm telling her it's boring, so she knows.
Right, but if people tell me I'm boring,
I'm like, fuck you, because I'm here trying my best.
They all means tell me fuck off and everything.
Oh, no, it's okay.
I mean, it's like, no, but I mean,
but I try to keep it interesting.
I mean, it's like, that's why I just let people up
and stuff like that, like, it's kind of like,
whatever happens, happens on the show is like,
You know, we never know it. It's like unpredictable and there's a lot of different
I always only hear like where to go what to do like do this do that like this is a bad idea
You're a little blurry. I need to like learn things on my own, you know
It feels worse for if we carefully trust like who give you advice
We can love agendas and stuff, but
I'm pretty sure
I think someone was trying to give her, like for example, someone's trying to give her an idea of like, oh, you should stream on a cruise ship.
I was like, you know, you know how much money you're going to pay for Wi-Fi on a cruise ship at least, so don't do that.
You know, like shit like that. It wasn't all trolling.
Right, I mean, there's good advice thrown in to throw them off a little bit. Oh
That's the thing she knows that I'm one of the people who could take it or leave it but she banned me so I left it
Yeah, like you were
I have a friend named piranha
And I used to like have her like, you know, say, oh, go to check out the chat, listen to me in her chat
And then she said something about
It wasn't even like criticism. It was kind of like a comment about oh, you know, you know about
Getting donations or something. I don't remember exactly what it was
But it's like it was something that at least got real offended over and she likes to she blocked her and it wasn't meant to be offensive
She was like things like that like I don't think I actually meant to hurt her
But she took it that way
Like the shit that I said after she banned me. Yeah, that was meant to piss her off. I don't even remember what I was but like
The the communities that I come from like beyond the trailer and mundane Matt
Like people like that. Those are my friends that are on YouTube people that I actually know
Like that I've actually seen in real life. So if you look at the on the trailer that lady like she is
She is like really on her game
Like in the Hollywood industry her name is Grace Randolph. Okay, like she's on her game
Matt Jarbo he used to be on his game when it came to like Gamergate or a video game
Whatever the fuck he used to do. I've been on their shows. I know them like Alyssa had the opportunity
To like actually work with someone who has access to like a warehouse full of props
And I was kind of like testing the waters for a year
For year I was testing the waters to try to see if she was worth working with and part of that testing is criticism
If you cannot take a little bit of criticism about body or being boring
You don't deserve to have access to the things that I have access to so in the end. She just kind of lost
access
But I
Think as a person she could go farther is she takes her medication. We're on the same medication
but uh
What is it? Hold on. It's Xanax
Not just Xanax. There's the mood stabilizer. There's some depression shit going in there, too
Okay, like it like there's nothing that people have said
That is that bad where she should be quitting or body
She shouldn't be botting right now, but I like I said people can buy bots for I was being like someone like the guy joker that I
Oh, like buy them for you. That's a different scenario. Yeah, like when I confronted her about it
leaf confirmed it
It was wrong I'm like, oh like
The king does it for like I think in that you know
He was doing that like he was but it was and so she probably knew about it, but it's like
Well, maybe I, like, embarrassed her on accident, like, you know.
Or is that a little too meta, like, to reveal it a little too much, because it's, like, you know, it's kind of, like...
Like, you'll see this whole situation makes me feel like half bad, half not bad.
I don't know, like, it's complicated with her.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, it's the whole heiress thing. Yes, she has that energy. Yes, it's chaos. It's chaos like personified
You know in a human and a beautiful woman, right? It's like yeah, but I think I'm also a little too chaotic
Like if we were to actually work, yeah, it wouldn't be good. It wouldn't end well
Because I'm not Andy dick, you know, I'm not a bitch
right
I mean he wasn't even I mean if they were engaged, but I mean I never even saw them in person
I think I saw them in person like one time. It was very awkward. It was like
He was we look for a sidekick types
She looks for sidekick sidekick not psychic. I think yeah
Yeah, she wants to rob into her Batman. She wants, you know, she wants to be a joker and she wants to Harley Quinn.
She likes the bad boys, she likes bad boys too, and she has so many simps that it's like the bad boys look even more attractive to her.
The bad boys are just like, I think these like they're kind of mentally unstable and they're being as like Spartan.
She said Spartan was hot, dude. Do you think Spartan's hot?
No, but he's like so mean that that's like what she likes. I think that's what she's attracted
She's attracted to that and like the other dude that she hit what's his name?
Skora the score. Oh, yeah, and and then Eric Eric to I don't know my god
I felt bad for Skora because of his disease, but then he was such an asshole then I felt bad for her
But then she was so mean to him
Yeah, well she wouldn't get off live stream and like and then and then he would you know, he sent her $2 million or something over super challenge or
I don't blame her for like being confused about that scenario. That's someone sending me $2 million. I wouldn't get off streams easily.
It's like all of a sudden and then it's like so he's expecting like a long time with her like where they can like make out or something
I don't know and she just wants to be on stream 24-7 day like
in case something illegal happens.
I don't know, I don't know if she's like,
so it's just with a recipe for disaster.
I never thought I would see her like hit people
or hit someone, but if it was gonna happen,
it would be when she is getting cheated on
or something like that.
That's when it was.
Well, I don't think she hit me she's like
She hit me no, I'm not saying no. I mean like I'm not saying that she did anything wrong. I would have done the same thing
Yeah, I would have hit him too
Yeah, I'm just saying I never thought I would have like she was probably been pissed
Well, that's like we're gonna get a good marriage because she's like not give a fuck like she didn't care like she's on the stream
That lady that lady was pissed
Yeah.
He's lucky that she didn't have like a knife or peppers.
She didn't have pepper spray.
Never.
Yeah.
Let it be a lesson.
Just like, don't cheat on people.
Maybe break up with someone.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess he was trying to, I'll never, I'll never bring her blame her for the way
she acted on that day because like, I've been in a relationship where people are cheating
or whatever.
It drives you insane.
I'm with her like, if she wasn't taking her meds, that shit's not going to go well in
her brain.
Yeah, it's gonna be a manic situation. Yeah, I just like that too like we're legit the same like
She got more trouble right? Yeah, she got she got charged. Yeah
Being a charge and he like he like pulled her hair. He like almost sort of sort of passengers. Yeah, but in Florida stand your ground
Yeah, he hit first. So yeah, which is kind of
but like
Yeah, like the whole thing with the wheel
Grabbing the wheel you're on the highway. You could kill everybody. What are you doing in school? Yeah
That could be that should be like an endangerment of public safety. I mean, there's something it's just whatever they decide to charge you
I don't know what they like. They like just like let him like
Go and then they did it's like they probably looked at his daddy and was like, okay. We don't deal with the Saudi
Yeah, exactly, but yeah, I mean it's like I guess having a father that's again, you know Saudi Arabian Prince or whatever he is
I mean it's good. It's good an oil magnet
By the way, there's 23 people watching us 23 people should be liking the stream guys
But 23 doesn't mean W so I guess they'll be I got a win right? Thank you guys
23 likes that. I don't think so
Actually on tick tock if I go to tick tock and do readings and stuff for like an hour
I can get like 5,000 likes because it's like people can like multiple times
But people will literally sit there for like the entire time liking my stream
Like there's people that are like that cool and nice and it's like and then I go to my stream here
I'm on for like six hours with like a hundred people and there's like less than 10 likes. I'm like, what the
YouTube is tough. It's hard guys. It's like there ain't no joke guys
Yeah
It's a relief not being a
Not being monetized on it because I got a few of them
Yeah
No, I know we got 25 people that is actually like I started out probably like five people in my chat
Right when I started out probably just regular streaming last year and but I would go to communities
I would go to another shows I would meet people and I develop relationships
And then it's like and then they would bring their friends and they bring their friends and it's like it builds
But it's like you do have to like
Network a little bit in these communities and just like at least like make yourself known and then sometimes maybe getting up
I'm not suggesting getting a fight with somebody on purpose, but it will happen
I had a lot of drama bringing a lot of people and it's like but it's like at that same time
It's like it also it just brings a lot of trolls and then it's all yeah, that's the thing. Do you want your whole audience?
I'm holding my bar here. That's how I am. Do you want your whole audience to like be a bunch of trolls?
Mine is, but it's like you said, you're like, yeah, I'm a little bit of a troll, like I, my, my Trollopedia, I like, I'm like the Troll King in the book, like, and it's like, I'm only a troll king because genetically I'm like Troll Royalty, but I like, you know.
But I'm looking nice my nicer troll. I'm one of the nicer ones that it's kind of more self-aware and like not like trying to be mean or
I think there you guess it's trolling can be so funny and then it gets to a point where it's like
Oh, then it goes into illegal territory, but it's funny up to that point, right? It's like yeah, don't make people hurt themselves in Minecraft
Don't cry it. I mean you can like make fun of somebody. I mean like there's this joke
I wouldn't got fish tacos. I'm up here like a few times and everything
So there's all these like then I did this stream
Whereas like I'm turning into a fish taco and then at my
Guy animated me crying on it and stuff like that. I probably can play it real quick. It's pretty funny
This is like last year. This is Lord of the Groove channel. This guy's name is Lord of the Groove and
He made a few cartoons about me. I was scared cuz I was like, oh my gosh like
they're gonna make fun of me and stuff but it's actually pretty funny because it's just like my
whatever I really was saying plus their animation um
need to see this hit from the bong hit from the bong chat yeah get hit from the bong and
he usually covers like cyrax and stuff he's this whole goblin tail thing like cyrax hit and see
I am not the gay cyrax by the way guys what are you
Okay, here we go. Okay, so
Yeah, that one it's terrible. Okay, so this is this is um Lord of the Groove
So funny, I mean, yeah, they got they got me on this one here you go
I'm turning into a fish top. Oh guys. I mean, oh, I'm becoming a fish
It's probably my last night here, man I choked it as a fish taco sooner or later I know what would happen
I just can't stop eating them they're so good I eat them so fast
I'm like I've turned into a fish taco basically
But I just need a tortilla wrap. That's why I put my blanket around me. It feels like I'm feels like I'm a burrito
I feel like I'm turning to fish taco. I'm sorry guys. I'm turning fish taco
I hate too many of them
And it was like they made you look like fun. It was like oh, this is good and then turn into an addiction
So I've turned into a fish taco. All I need to do is wrap myself in a blanket and turn myself into a burrito
And that's gonna be the end of it guys. I'm sorry
With that one and actually there was a couple more let me see
They have the Mexican pizza lady that I was eating these Mexican pizza ladies coming to my door
It's new are your pizza?
Okay, we have we have
You guys guys I can't even guys I can't even read the disgusting
Text messages I got today, and they're confused Mexican women who are delivering the pizzas
Senor, oh
Like hello as was it paid for?
Okay, and there's like there like it was a paper they're like no senior and I was like oh I was like Los Hentos
It's like it's a prank some prank and she's like, okay. Okay. She left
Have it three times in a row though
Yeah, that's that one. Wow, and there's one more this is the
classic
the butthole scam
You got scammed by a butthole and so maybe all those things are true
Maybe those things are true, but you know this time of this time. I already know the butthole scam. I'm not falling for it again
Okay
I'm not paying to see a butthole until I see it first. Okay, I
Will pay you after you show me your butthole, but you can't just
Say you're gonna show me your butthole and then I send you a $10 cash up and then you don't show me your butthole
It's not acceptable. Okay. Hey guys, that's the new rule. It's a new rule. You're just show it to me first
Maybe I'll give you a tip
Please nobody
That'd be weird because then I would be like oh then Aldi would do it or something and I really like oh god. Yeah, I
Know and then I want like I you know, I'd like a man to do it like but you know
I see never never mind. It sounds too expensive. It's not there. I mean it too many buttholes
Too many buttholes in the world too little money. So
Hey, act last you told you about this channel you remember later. Okay. Hey act. Thank you
22 likes that I gave it 22 likes. Thank you guys. You're awesome. Yay. See they listened
Thank you for sharing. Yeah, I think we're gone. Wow 22. It's a big 22 guys
Thank you, but those are funny clips though. I mean, I uh, I appreciated those and so I
Love it. Thank you
Sincical ramblings
animated
Yeah, we kind of have like that old-school
animation like early 2000s animation
Right, you ever you ever watch dr. Katz. That was a funny show or the critic you remember the shows
John Lovitz was the critic
No, they don't call me central
And then they have done dr. Katz was like kind of like a really low budget cartoon with this little Jewish like high interest
But they had all these celebrities come on it and be animated and like
They'd be all weird
Yeah
John Leavitt's
Hey
Niggerless cage
Niggerless cage John
Yeah, said are you John's old interviews were pretty classic. Oh fucking John. Yeah
Because when he used well he used to be like, you know when he would do that
You go up to like, what's her name, Meryl Streep?
Not Meryl Streep, but Kathleen Turner.
The idea of fart on the set, she's like, never.
Never.
Yep.
Those are classic.
I also like the Richard and Sal Frank phone calls,
like the Trey Yo calls and the,
Also Eric the midget to I was Eric the midget used to like listen to like you know
Put it on me for one to sleep like a 10-hour stream, and I'd have like Eric the midget dreams all night
Pretty disturbing, but interesting
Poor guy died Eric the midget
Does anyone else died like I who who's died it's Howard's parents still alive because I mean I just remember
I was like aren't they like a hundred years old. That was like 20 years
No, I think the dad is dead for sure, okay
Holy shit.
It would be like on the news.
Howard Stern's father is passed away.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. His mom's alive, but Ben.
Ben? When did he die?
In 22.
Oh, 2022.
July. He was 99.
Wow.
I remember that he had prostate cancer.
Okay, yeah, that's tough getting it that old, yeah, I mean that's what always does it like some kind of cancer Wednesday eventually
I mean it's eventually it's always cancer at the end you like
I don't know if you've noticed.
Eventually some people, sometimes it's gonna be too late to cure.
I mean, that's the thing, I mean, it's like.
Yeah, cancer only kills you when you're weak, I guess.
Well, no, cause it's a aggressive cancer.
You know what, I'm talking about.
Yeah, I mean, it's a good, a lot of times it will spread
before they like catch it, you know,
it's like, cause it's like,
it won't have too many symptoms or, and then now.
It wears down your immune system.
Yeah, I'll go into your like lymph nodes,
and then it's a pot, like once it gets spreads,
it's impossible to like stop it if you get it.
At a certain point like this prostate cancer prostate cancer is very curable if it's caught on time
That's why it's important to have a prostate exam and stuff. Um, I gotta do that. Yeah
We're gonna do a self-exam and you'll save a lot of money
Let's see. Yeah, look up how to do a prostate
Just feel around for lumps like
Wait, wait, we got a lump over here
Yeah, yeah, but uh, yeah, it's terrible. It's terrible, but we all
At least it happens for like a lot of people like at the same time, but that's pretty old 99 years old
That's the life, you know, that's like oh, we should just let you a hundred you like lip-slept
See what year is it 2025? So you look through the Great Depression often practically look through World War two
You've been through like the worst already. That's when they're in children, right?
And so it's like they're probably
Everything is like, you know easy after that
Kind of weeder you smoking
Um, I have like this vape right here. I might get another one because this baby is like on the left drag
There's like a term vape and then I just like some a little tobacco
Yeah, my cigar, so
I've got some indica right here. Oh
Nice, let me show you another hit off this. I can see it. I can see I'll code it around the chat for my next command
You're gonna pay for a membership to this man's channel
All right, everyone needs to pay for a membership to this man's channel. Thank you 30 of you
And because I don't have the membership set up for the I have
I do but I do have cult of psyche I do have the membership available there now
I'm moving over there, and so it's like just it's five dollars, but there are a couple a few tiers and
You can if you want to get in early because I'm still working the website a little bit
You can like go ahead and send a cash out donation. I'll make sure to put you in the list give you the correct initiation and
You know, members will get like readings and like the upper tier members will get actually they can call me
Or like have a two two fifteen minute phone call or one thirty minute phone call every month
Talk about anything you want to talk about and do reading or talk about
AI music or whatever you want to talk about because i'm
Pretty good at you want more cartoons. Jamie like the cartoon. Yeah
Jamie's my recommend his tarot readings. They're very accurate. Thank you. Thank you so much. Yeah, I uh
I've been doing tarot actions since I was eight years old.
I got my first deck when I was eight years old.
So I'm not 44.
So how long is that?
Like 36 years or something like that?
Or three years?
We definitely don't look 44.
Thank you for your age look like they're happy if you don't look half dead
Good job. You have good genetics. Well, my dad used to be like I used to go to breakfast with them
He he was in his 80s and my dad was like at his 80s. He was a Gemini a Gemini's a very um
Energetic they're very energetic. They have a lot of like
Oh, does your mom like to talk with the phone or like she doesn't stop talking? Yeah
They're the talkers of the zodiac. They'll talk about anything anybody anytime, right? But uh
Yeah, but he would go in and he'd be like, oh, I went to high school with that guy. We see something and be like this man
And a walker like he would just be like just like dried up like a prune and like
Barely be able to move my dad was just like he my dad was still working. He was still going to the office
He was still going to parties like probably five nights a week
You know he did a more active social life than any of my like, you know siblings and they're 30s and 40s
Right is like you they're just going out all the time
Unfortunately, he did like last year passed away like very suddenly, but he was 85 and so did live
a long life, but he was but he looked really good for his age. Capricorns also, we kind of aged backwards.
You know, so I think you look you look pretty good for your age too. I mean we both do.
Oh yeah, like a Jewish rat.
Well, I
Think you're I think you're very attractive. Well, you say I don't like I don't like the way my smile looks I look a little
Road and you're self-conscious about a few things I think hey, oh gets Joe Johnny. Do you know who's uh, this is the J.D.
Johnny
Oh, Joanie. Hi, Joanie. How are you doing girl? I
Have a story about Johnny, but I don't think I
Oh, she says okay, then we can tell I don't know. I don't know what I'm told them
But he and Joanie broke up on the phone. Uh-oh months ago
Yeah, she's like I
Mean as I said earlier when we were talking about Joanie two streams ago. I love the woman
I think that she's a nice lady. I
Love that she loves animals
And I think that she is a good friend to Elisa Giordano.
I agree with all those things.
Everyone in the chat should all pray for Joni,
because she needs our strength.
She needs our strength, everybody.
I have a few Joni songs actually.
Oh, I'll play a Joni song, I wanna hear this.
Do you wanna hear a Joni song?
Fuck yeah.
Okay, I'll find it. I'll see if I can find it. I do have it at the end. Let me see.
Then, yeah, I have the joys. You know, she would get these like, you know, people would like to do these parody songs.
We're kind of rude and I was like, you deserve her like a nice, a nice song about you, like, because she's a pretty good hearted person.
Is this one? Let's see.
That's not it. Okay.
It was a bigger minute, such a, I only have like a thousand songs. Let's see.
Come on, let's go. Yeah, because the Johnny, the Johnny song is actually great. Did this one?
Is it about Al?
Um, nope. I don't think Al is in the song, but I love Al.
I love that name, yeah, I love that name, Al.
That cat looked like it had a great life.
Rest in peace, Al.
Well, I don't know if I can find the video,
but I will play the song.
I can't find the song for sure.
So the song is, let me see, do you know what I mean?
I have the same tune.
Yeah, I have, okay.
Okay, I'll put on the song.
Just a second minute.
Okay, is it bad here is
This is your imagination
Every fall became a step I had to take
Yeah, he had to go take care of something, so I'm gonna
I'm gonna play another video while he's coming back. Let me see
What do I got? I got
I'm sure I have a good video for you
What do we got?
What's up?
You're back?
Oh, I think he's still gone.
Well, let me see, it's six o'clock.
I might come on a little later.
I do wanna thank JD so much for being on the show
and I hope you had fun
and I hope you will wanna come back.
I wanna thank everyone for being here tonight.
I'm gonna go grab another beer and see what's up tonight.
But thank you guys so much, so much fun.
Thank you JD.
JD, come back again real soon, love you, okay?
I believe you're the real JD.
Have fun guys. I'll see you a little bit later tonight, okay?
I'll see you later. Well, I'm gonna add a song. Here you go.
Airplane mode I felt it in my skin
So I was sitting like design ago
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing we've learned
Not to be celestial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is cynical
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you god damn head
I knew you craved the chaos I fed
Cause love like cars ain't never dead
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I wanna crush you
I could never
I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial
But you made my pain perpetual
So I did something sexual
Just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from a stranger's lair
Just to prove that I still care
You'd fall apart cause you know it's true
No one sins the way I do
Not to be divine
But I love you
That's a beautiful